heartbowsmakeup.com 2018-11-20

# Privacy Policy - Heart Bows & Makeup - Indian Makeup & Beauty Blog, Indian Fashion Blog, Indian Beauty Blog, Delhi Beauty & Fashion Blog, Indian Skincare Blog, Eye Makeup Tutorials, Product Reviews, OOTD

This Privacy Policy governs the manner in which **Heart Bows & Makeup** collects, uses, maintains and discloses information about the users (each, a “User”) of the [http://www.heartbowsmakeup.com](http://www.heartbowsmakeup.com/ "Heart Bows & Makeup") website (“Site” or “Blog”). This privacy policy applies to the website and all services provided by Heart Bows & Makeup.

#### Personal identification information

We may collect personal identification information from Users in various ways, including, but not limited to, when Users visit our website, subscribe to the newsletters, fill out a form, and in connection with other activities, giveaways, services, features or resources that are available on our website. Users may be asked for name, email address, phone number and other information where required. Users may, if they wish, visit our Site anonymously. We will collect personal identification information from Users only if they voluntarily submit such information on the Site, by filling a form or by contacting us via email. Users can always refuse to supply personally identification information, except that it may prevent them from participating in certain Site related activities such as competitions and giveaways.

#### Non-personal identification information

We collect non-personal identification information about Users whenever they interact with our Site. Non-personal identification information may include the browser name, the type of computer and technical information about Users means of connection to our Site, such as the operating system and the ISP (Internet service providers) they are using and other similar information.

#### Web browser cookies

“Cookies” are small files that stores information about User’s web browser, their device (mobile and/or computer) and other information like website settings. Our Site uses “cookies” to improve User experience. User’s web browser places cookies on their device storage (hard drive or other storage device) for record-keeping purposes and sometimes to track information about them. User may choose to set their web browser to refuse cookies, or to alert User when cookies are being sent by changing settings of their web browser. If they do so, note that some parts of the Site may not work as expected and function properly. Along with our Site, to provide services by third party websites on our Site and/or to collect non-personal information about the user, third party cookies are also stored on User’s device.

#### How we use collected information

Heart Bows & Makeup may collect and use User’s personal information for purposes mentioned as following:

  * **To personalize user experience**  
We may use information to understand how our Users as a group use the services and resources provided on our Site. This information is used to improve User’s experience
  * **To improve our Site**  
We may use feedback provided by Users to improve our Site, products and services from time to time.
  * **To run a promotion, contest, giveaways  or other Site feature**  
We may use the collected information to send Users information they agreed to receive about topics we think will be of interest to them.
  * **To send periodic emails about our Site and its services**  
We may use the email address to respond to User’s inquiries, questions, and/or other requests made by User. If User decides to opt-in to our mailing list, they will receive emails that may include company news, updates, related posts/products or service information, etc. If at any time the User would like to unsubscribe from receiving future emails, we include detailed unsubscribe instructions at the bottom of each email they receive or User may contact us via our Site and/or email.

#### How we protect User’s information

We adopt appropriate data collection, storage and processing practices and security measures to protect against unauthorized access, disclosure or destruction of User’s personal information like username, password, transaction information and data stored on our Site and third party web apps used by our Site.

#### Sharing User’s personal information

We do not sell, trade, or rent Users personal identification information to others that they (“User”) choose to share with us. We may share generic aggregated demographic information not linked to any personal identification information regarding visitors and users with our business partners, trusted affiliates, trusted sponsors and advertisers for the purposes outlined above. We may use third party service providers to help us operate our Site or administer activities on our behalf, such as sending out newsletters or surveys. We may share User’s information with these third parties for those limited purposes provided that User have given us their (User’s) permission.

#### Third party websites

Users may find advertising or other content on our Site that link to the sites (“websites”) and services of our partners, suppliers, advertisers, sponsors, licensors and other third parties. We do not control the content or links that appear on these sites and are not responsible for the practices employed by these websites linked to or from our Site. In addition, these sites or services, including their content and links, may be constantly changing according to their updation. These sites and services may have their own privacy policies which is separated from privacy policy of our Site. Browsing and interaction on any other website, including websites which have a link to our Site, is subject to that website’s own terms and policies and User’s own decision.

#### Google Adsense and other ad vendors

Some of the ads may be served by Google and other ad vendors on our website. Google’s use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to Users based on their visit to our Site and other sites. DART uses “non personally identifiable information” and does NOT track personal information about User, such as User’s name, email address, physical address, etc. User may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy at <http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html> . User may also opt out of third-party vendor’s use of cookies by visiting <http://www.aboutads.info/>

#### Changes to this privacy policy

Heart Bows & Makeup has the right to update this privacy policy at any time without any notification. However when we do, we will revise the updated date at the bottom of this page. We encourage Users to frequently check this page for any changes in our privacy policies to stay informed about how we are helping to protect the personal information we collect. You acknowledge and agree that it is your responsibility to review this privacy policy periodically and become aware of modifications in our privacy policy.

#### Your acceptance of these terms

By using this Site, you signify your acceptance of this policy. If you do not agree to this policy, please do not use our Site. Your continued use of the Site following the posting of changes to this policy will be deemed your acceptance of those changes.

#### Contacting us

If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this site, please contact us at:  
Heart Bows & Makeup  

_This document was last updated on June 23, 2014_
